테리, 제가 일 한지
얼마 안된 건 알지만
Terry, I know I haven't worked here
very long but would it be possible...
혹시 백 달러만 가불할 수
있을까요?
...if I got a $1 00 advance
on my salary?
An advance?
가불?
추수감사절을 가족과
보내려구요
So I can spend
Thanksgiving with my family.
매년 베일에서 스키를 타는데
아빠가 돈을 내주셨거든요
Every year we ski in Vail,
and my father pays for my ticket.
But I've started
this independent thing...
이제 성인인데 독립해야죠
그래서 이 일도 하는 거구요
...which is actually why
I took this "job. "
Rachel, Rachel, sweetheart!
레이첼, 우리 아가씨
You' re a terrible, terrible waitress.
넌 아주 일을 못하는
웨이트리스야
Really, really awful.
진짜 해도 너무해
무슨 말씀인지 알아요
주제파악은 해요
I hear what you're saying.
I'm with you.
저도 노력하고 있어요
점점 나아지고 있구요
But I'm trying really hard,
and I think I'm doing better.
정말이에요
I really do.
-Does anybody need coffee?
-Yeah, over here.
커피 필요하신 분?
여기요, 나두요
Look at that.
The One Where Underdog Gets Away
Excuse me, sir? Hi.
You come in here all the time.
실례합니다, 손님
여기 단골이시죠?
올 때마다 주실 팁을
미리 주시면 안될까요?
Do you think there's a possibility
that you could advance me my tips?
괜찮아요, 손님
Okay, okay. That's fine. Fine.
Sorry about that spill before!
아까 물 쏟은 거 죄송해요
Only 98.50 to go!
이제 98달러 남았어
안녕
Did you know Mom and Dad are going
to Puerto Rico for Thanksgiving?
- 어서 와
- 안녕
추수감사절 때, 부모님이
푸에르토리코에 가신대
뭐? 아니야
-What? No, they're not.
-Yes, the Blymans invited them.
맞아, 초대받고 가신대
그럴 리가 없어
You' re wrong.
그럴 리가 있어
-I am not wrong.
-You' re wrong.
그럴 순 없어
방금 들은 얘기야
No, I just talked to them.
I' m calling Mom.
엄마한테 전화해야지
얘들아!
-Hey, hey.
-Hey!
- 안녕
- 어서 와
And this from the Cry for Help
Department: Are you wearing makeup?
사회복지 센터 갔다 왔어?
근데 웬 화장이야?
오늘부터 난 공식적인
배우이자 모델이시다
Yes, I am. As of today, I'm officially
Joey T ribbiani, actor/model.
That's funny. I was thinking you look
more like, Joey T ribbiani, man/woman.
난 네가 오늘부터
남자이자 여자가 된 줄 알았어
-What were you modeling for?
-Posters for the free clinic.
이번엔 어디 모델 했어?
무료 시립병원 포스터 알지?
So you' re gonna be one
of those healthy guys?
그럼 그 포스터의
건장한 주인공이야?
- 천식 모델도 잘생겼더라
- 그래, 맞아
-The asthma guy's really cute.
-Know which one you'll be?
이번 포스터 주제는 뭐래?
잘 모르지만
관절염 얘기는 들었어
No, but I hear Lyme disease
is open, so you know....
-Good luck, man. I hope you get it.
-Thanks.
그 병에 걸리길 빌어
고맙다
You were right. How can they do this?
It's Thanksgiving!
네 말이 맞다
어떻게 그러실 수가 있지?
추수감사절인데
우리 집에서 식사하자
엄마랑 똑같이 요리해줄게
What if I cook dinner at my place?
I'll make it just like Mom's.
으깬 감자에 덩어리
넣어줄래?
Will you make mashed potatoes
with the lumps?
They're not actually supposed to
I'll work on the lumps.
꼭 그렇게 할 수
있다기 보다는...
그렇게 할게
-Joey, you' re going home?
-Yeah.
- 조이는 집에 가지?
- 응
Chandler, you' re still boycotting
all the pilgrim holidays?
챈들러는 아직도 청교도 휴가는
안 지내지?
-Every single one of them.
-Phoebe, you'll be with your grandma?
응, 절대로 안 지켜
피비는 할머니와 보낼 거야?
And her boyfriend.
할머니 남자친구도 같이
그런데 음력으로 해서
12월에 추수감사절을 할거야
We're celebrating Thanksgiving
in December because he's lunar.
So you're free Thursday then?
그럼 목요일엔 별 일 없지?
-Yeah. Oh, can I come?
-Yeah.
- 응, 껴도 돼?
- 응
-Rach, are you gonna make it to Vail?
-Absolutely. Shoop, shoop, shoop.
넌 아직도 베일에 갈 생각이니?
물론이지, 슉 슉 슉!
-Only $1 02 to go.
-I thought it was 98. 50?
102달러 남았어
아깐 98달러 남았다며?
그랬었는데...
컵을 깼어
Yeah, well, it was, but l
I broke a cup, so....
-Well, l' m off to Carol's.
-Ooh, ooh, why don't we invite her?
캐롤한테 가야겠다
참, 참, 캐롤도 초대해
Ooh, ooh, because she's my ex-wife
and will want to bring her...
참, 참, 내 전처는 싫어
온다고 해도
참, 참, 아마 레즈비언 친구와
같이 올걸
...ooh, ooh, lesbian life partner.
- 안녕
- 안녕!
Hi. Is Carol here?
- 캐롤 있어?
- 아니, 세미나에 갔어
-No, she's at a faculty meeting.
-I just came by to pick up my skull.
내 해골을 가지러 왔어
Well, not mine, but....
이 해골 말고...
-Come in.
-Thanks.
- 들어와
- 고마워
캐롤이 빌려갔는데
박물관에 돌려줘야 하거든
Carol borrowed it, and I have
to get it back to the museum.
어떻게 생긴 거야?
-What's it look like?
-Kind of like a big face without skin.
얼굴에 살이 없을걸
Yes. I'm familiar with the concept.
그렇겠지
나도 그럴 줄 알았어
- 직접 찾아봐
- 응
-We can just look for it.
-Okay.
Wow, you guys sure have a lot
of books about being a lesbian.
레즈비언이 되기 위한 책이
엄청 많네
모든 것엔 과정이 있어
Well, you know,
you have to take a course.
Otherwise they don't let you do it.
안 그러면 불가능한 거야
'토끼와 거북이'
고전동화지
Hey, Yertle the Turtle! A classic.
Actually, I'm reading it to the baby.
요즘 아기에게 읽어주고 있어
The baby that hasn't been born yet?
아직 태어나지 않은 애한테?
교육열이... 대단하다
Wouldn't that mean you're crazy?
You don't think
they can hear sounds in there?
뱃속에서 소리를 듣는 거 몰라?
농담이지?
진짜 얘길 한단 말야?
You' re not serious?
I mean, you really talk to it?
자주 해
아기가 내 목소리는 알아야지
Yeah, all the time.
I want the baby to know my voice.
Well, that's just
Do you talk about me?
내 얘기도 했어?
- 응, 많이 해줬어
- 정말?
-Yeah. All the time.
-Really?
But, we just refer to you
as " Bobo the Sperm Guy. "
아빠대신 '보보'라고 했어
아기씨 준 사람!
If she's talking to it, I just think
I should get some belly time too.
수잔도 한다는데
나도 대화를 하고 싶어
물론 믿지는 않지만
Not that I believe this.
I believe it. I think the baby
can hear everything.
난 믿어, 아기는 분명히
들을 수 있어
그래?
-Really?
-I'll show you. This'll seem weird.
내가 보여줄게
좀 이상할 거야
칠면조 안에 머리를 넣고
우리 말이 들리는지 봐
But you put your head
inside this turkey...
...and we'll all talk
and you'll hear everything we say.
I'd just like to say I'm totally
behind this experiment.
나 같으면 절대
그런 실험은 안 해
머리에 버터를 바르고 하던지
In fact, I'd very much like
to butter your head.
-Hey.
-Rach, did you make your money?
안녕, 레이첼
돈은 마련됐니?
아니, 한참 남았어
베일은 포기할까봐
No, not even close. Forget Vail.
Forget seeing my family.
가족 상봉도 날아갔고
'슉 슉 슉'도 끝났어
Forget shoop, shoop, shoop.
레이첼?
-Rach, here's your mail.
-Thanks. You can put it on the table.
- 편지 왔어
- 그래, 탁자에 올려놔
아니, 편지 왔다구!
No. Here's your mail!
Thanks. You can put it on the table!
알았어, 탁자에 올려놔
빨리 뜯어봐
Would you just open it!
Oh, my God! You guys are great!
어머!
정말 멋진 친구들이야!
We all chipped in.
우리가 조금씩 모았어
우리?
-We did?
-You owe me $20.
20달러 갚어
고마워, 너무 고맙다
Thank you. Thank you so much!
Chandler, got your traditional
holiday feast. T omato soup...
챈들러 먹을거리도
장을 봐왔는데
토마토 수프, 구운 치즈
그리고 양파 한 포대
...grilled-cheese fixings
and a family-size bag of Funyuns.
잠깐, 챈들러!
이게 추수감사절 음식이야?
This is your Thanksgiving dinner?
What is it with you and this holiday?
왜 이런 걸 먹는 건데?
-I'm 9 years old.
-I hate this story!
잘 들어, 9살 때...
또 시작이다
추수감사절 음식을
맛있게 먹었지
We've finished this magnificent
Thanksgiving dinner. I have...
특히 잊을 수 없는게
있었지
입 속에 호박파이를
넣는 순간에
...a mouthful of pumpkin pie.
내게 부모님의 이혼이
발표된 거야
And then my parents tell me
they're getting divorced.
Oh, my God!
너무해
Very difficult to enjoy Thanksgiving
dinner once you've seen it in reverse.
먹었던 음식을 다시
확인하는 게 아주 힘들었지
What's this?
I never saw this at Mom's.
이건 뭐야?
엄마는 이런 거 안 쓰셔
- 고구마야
- 뭐라구?
-It's a yam.
-Hello....
This isn't a yam.
Yam comes in purple cans.
추수감사절용 고구마는
보라색 캔으로 나와
They don't They don't come in these.
절대 이렇건 안 써
Ross, don't take this the wrong way
or anything, but back off.
엄마식대로
해달라는 건 알지만...
참견 마!
안녕하세요?
Hi.
- 우리 함께 일했죠?
- 그래요?
-We used to work together.
-We did?
Yeah, at Macy's.
You' re the Obsession girl, right?
메이시 백화점이요
- 옵세션 향수 홍보했죠?
- 네
-Yes.
-I was the Aramis guy.
난 아라미스 했었어요
아라미스... 아라미스...
-Aramis. Aramis. Aramis.
-Yeah, right!
기억나요
이건 진심인데
정말 잘 하던데요
-You' re the best in the business.
-Get out.
- 설마요
- 정말 대단했어요
You' re amazing! You know when
to spritz. You know when to lay back.
향수 뿌리고,
뒤로 빠지고...
정말이요?
정말 큰 격려가 되네요
Really? You don't know
what that means to me.
오늘도 향기가 좋은데
뭘 뿌렸죠?
You smell great tonight.
What are you wearing?
향수 안 써요
Nothing.
-Listen, do you wanna go get a drink?
-Yeah, that would be
어디 가서 한잔할래요?
네
왜요?
-What's wrong?
-I have to do something.
갑자기 할 일이 생각났어요
뭔데요?
What?
가야 되요
-Leave.
-Wait, wait, wait!
제발, 가지 말아요
성병 : 누가 걸렸는지
아무도 모릅니다
너희들도 봤구나?
So I guess you all saw it.
-What?
-Saw what?
- 뭘?
- 뭔데?
No, we' re just laughing. You know
how laughter can be infectious.
그냥 웃은 거야
웃음은 전염되잖아
- 안녕
- 나도 좀 끼워 주라
Set another place for Thanksgiving.
My entire family thinks I have VD.
부모님은 내가 성병
걸린 줄 알아
"T onight, on a very special Blossom. "
제발 전염만 시키지 마
잘 되고 있어
Looking good! Okay!
Cider's mulling, turkey's turkeying,
yams are yamming....
사과술에다, 칠면조도 굽고
고구마도 잘 익고...
What?
왜?
I don't know. It's just not
the same without Mom in the kitchen.
아냐,
그냥 엄마 생각이 나서
알았으니까
사람 괴롭히지 말고 나가
Get out and stop annoying me!
엄마랑 비슷하다
Oh, that's closer.
비행기표 샀어
5시간 후면, 슉 슉 슉!
I got the tickets!
Five hours from now,
shoop, shoop, shoop!
슉 소리 좀 그만해
-Oh, you must stop shooping.
-Okay, l' m gonna get my stuff.
짐이나 챙겨야지
얼굴 좀 펼 수 없어?
Will you come in?
I prefer to keep a safe distance
from all this merriment.
즐거운 분위기에서
떨어져 있으려구
비켜! 호박파이 나가신다
Look out! Incoming pumpkin pie!
We laughed when you did it with
the stuffing, but that's not funny.
이제 우리가 웃었으니까
나쁜 일이 생길 거야
모니카, 질문 있어
왜 튀긴 감자가 없니?
Hey, Monica, I got a question.
I don't see any T ator T ots.
그게 질문이야?
-That's not a question.
-My mom makes them. It's a tradition.
엄마가 늘 해주던
가족 전통이야
You get a piece of turkey on your fork,
a little cranberry sauce and a T ot!
칠면조 고기를 잘라서
크랜베리 소스에 찍어
튀긴 감자도!
그 놈의 성병 때문에
가족도 못 보러 가다니...
I mean, it's bad enough I can't be
with my family because of my disease.
All right. Fine.
알았어
으깬 감자와 튀긴 감자
다 만들어줄게
Tonight's potatoes will be mashed,
with lumps and in the form of Tots.
난 미래의 우리 아가
만나러 간다
All right, I'm off
to talk to my unborn child.
엄마는 안 때렸어
Okay, Mom never hit.
이제 다 됐어
Okay, all done.
Phoebe, did you whip the pota?
Ross needs lumps!
그냥 다 으깼어?
오빠는 덩어리가 있어야돼
미안해
Oh, l' m sorry! I just
콩과 양파를 넣으려면
다 으깨야하는 줄 알았어
I thought we could have them whipped
and then add some peas and onions.
Why do that?
그걸 왜 넣는데?
Because then they'd be just like my
mom used to make it, before she died.
우리 엄마가 늘 하시던
방식이야
돌아가시기 전에
이제,
감자는 세 종류가 됐군
Okay. Three kinds
of potatoes coming up.
Okay. Goodbye, you guys!
Thanks for everything!
잘 있어, 얘들아
모두들 고마워
어머, 미안해! 정말!
Oh, God, look at
Sorry! I'm so sorry.
An unbelievable thing happened!
Underdog got away!
놀라운 일이 터졌어
슈퍼맨이 떴어
-The balloon?
-No, no, the actual cartoon character.
풍선이?
아니, 실제로 떴다
물론 풍선이지
Of course the balloon!
뉴스에 나왔는데
백화점 앞에서 끈이 풀렸대
He broke free and was spotted
flying over Washington Square Park.
광장 쪽으로 날아갔대
옥상에 가서 볼 사람?
-I'm going to the roof. Who's with me?
-I can't!
난 가야돼
끈 풀린 2미터 짜리 풍선이
흔하니?
An 80-foot dog over the city?
How often does that happen?
큰 구경거리지
Almost never.
- 열쇠 있어?
- 그래
-Got the keys?
-Okay.
어서 해봐
Anytime you' re ready.
알았어, 해볼게
Okay. Okay, here we go.
여기다 대고 말하면 돼?
Okay. Where am I talking to here?
왠지 청각 실험하는
기분이 들어서...
There is one way that offers a
certain acoustical advantage, but....
일단 해봐!
Just aim for the bump.
알았어
할거야, 하겠어
Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay, here goes.
안되겠어, 난 못해
You know, I can't do this. This is
기분 이상해
바보가 된 기분이야
It's too weird. I feel stupid.
It's fine. You don't have to do it
just because Susan does it.
그럼 안 해도 돼
수잔을 따라할 필요 없어
안녕, 아기야!
안녕
Hello, baby. Hello. Hello.
the moment we first saw
the dog shadow fall over the park!
풍선 그림자가
광장을 다 덮었어
그런데 터뜨린 이유가 뭘까?
어차피 바람 빠지는데
But did they have to shoot him down?
That was just mean.
지금쯤이면 칠면조가
노릇노릇 맛있게 구워졌을 거야
Right now the turkey should
be crispy on the outside...
...and juicy on the inside.
Why are we standing here?
빨리 들어가자
We're waiting for you to open
the door. You have the keys.
빨리 문 열어
열쇠 너한테 있잖아
아니, 없어
No, I don't.
너한테 있어, 나올 때
열쇠 있어라고 했잖아
Yes, you do. When we left,
you said, "Got the keys. "
아니,
난 "열쇠 있어?"라고 했어
No, I didn't. I asked, "Got the keys? "
아냐,
네가 "열쇠 있어"라고 했어
No, no, no. You said, "Got the keys! "
Do either of you have the keys?
둘 다 열쇠가 없단 소리야?
-The oven is on!
-I've gotta get my ticket!
오븐이 켜있어!
비행기 시간 늦겠어
우리 집에 복사해 둔 게 있어
-Wait! We have a copy of your key.
-Get it!
그럼 빨리 가져와!
그렇게 소지 지르면 못 가
That tone won't make me go any faster.
- 조이?
- 좀 낫군
-Joey.
-That one will.
다들 그러더라구
빨리 전공을 정해
And everyone's telling me,
"You gotta pick a major. "
그래서 과감히 고생물학을
선택했단다
So on a dare, I picked paleontology.
And you have no idea what I'm saying,
because, face it, you' re a fetus.
내 말이 좀 어렵겠지만
넌 태아니까, 넘어가자
그래도 이제 정자 꼬리는
없잖니?
You're happy you don't
have gills anymore.
말하는 게 불편하면
노래를 불러 줘
You don't have to talk to it.
You can sing
배에 대고 노래는 못해
Please. I am not singing
to your stomach, okay?
잘 지냈어?
How's it going?
우리가 간다, 거리를 걸으며
제일 웃긴 얼굴을 찾아봐
Here we come
Walking down the street
Get the funniest looks from
Everyone we meet
헤이! 헤이!
Hey, hey
- 지금 느꼈어?
- 응
-Hey, did you just feel that?
-I did.
- 항상 이래?
- 아니, 처음이야
-Does it always?
-That was the first.
노래 계속 해봐
IKeep singing! IKeep singing!
헤이, 헤이
넌 나의 아가야
Hey, hey, you 're my baby
And I can 't wait to meet you
빨리 만나고 싶어 죽겠어
When you come out I'll buy you a bagel
Then we 'll go to the zoo
네가 나오면 빵도 사주고
동물원도 데려 갈게
- 또 발로 찼어
- 나도 느꼈어! 계속 해!
-lt did it again!
-I felt it that time!
헤이, 난 네 아빠란다
물론 가슴은 없지
Hey, hey, I'm your daddy
I'm the one without any breasts
잘됐다, 벌써 5시야
내 비행기는 물 건너갔다
This is great. It's 5:00. My plane
is pulling away from the gate.
나중 걸 타면 돼
-Maybe you can take a later flight.
-There is none.
나중 비행기는 없어
그럼 내일 가
-You can go tomorrow.
-T omorrow is not Thanksgiving!
내일이면 추수감사절이 끝나
친구가 좋은 말을 하면
듣는 척이라도 하면 안돼?
If l' m gonna cheer you up,
you have to meet me halfway.
Can you go any faster?
더 빨리 할 수 없어?
구멍 한 개에, 열쇠는 수십 개야
산수 할 줄 알지?
I got one keyhole and a zillion keys!
You do the math.
대체 뭔 열쇠가 그리 많아?
Why do you guys have so many
keys in there anyway?
이런 비상시를 대비해서
For an emergency just like this.
All right. Listen, smirky!
자꾸 이죽거릴래?
멍청히 풍선 구경만 안 했어도
난 벌써 비행기에 탔을 거야
If not for your stupid balloon,
I'd be on a plane...
...watching a woman do this... right
now. But l' m not!
You said you had the keys!
분명히 네가 있다고 했어
아냐, 열쇠를 갖고 있었으면
묻지도 않았을 거야
No, I didn't! I wouldn't say I had
the keys unless I had the keys!
됐어! 열쇠 얘기 그만해
더 이상 하지마
That's it! Enough with the keys.
No one say keys!
왜 내가 갖고 있다고 생각해?
Why would I have the keys?!
그럼 열쇠 얘기를 왜 했어?
-Aside from the fact you said you did?
-I didn't!
- 안 그랬어
- 그래도 너 밖에 없어
-You should've.
-Why?
- 왜?
- 왜냐면
-Because!
-Why?
- 왜?
- 왜냐면
전부 내 책임이라는 거야?
저녁식사 준비로도 충분치 않아?
Everything's my responsibility?
Isn't it enough that l' m making dinner?
Everyone wants a different kind
of potato, so I'm making them.
다들 감자 요리법이 달라서
난 세 종류나 만들었어
Does anybody care what kind
of potatoes I want? No!
내가 어떤 감자요리를
좋아하는지 알기나 해?
아니, 관심도 없겠지
No! No!
Just as long as Phoebe gets her peas
and onions, and Mario gets his T ots
피비는 감자에 콩과 양파를 넣고
조이는 튀긴 감자를 달래
It's my first Thanksgiving, and l
처음 하는 추수감사절 요리가
전부 다 타버렸어, 난...
It's all burnt, and I can't....
Monica, only dogs can hear you now.
Look, the door's open. Here we go.
동네방네 다 듣겠다
- 문 열렸어, 가자
- 세상에...
이거 잘 간직해
-All right, Chandler, don't lose this.
-No
안돼, 안돼...
칠면조가 다 탔어!
Well, the turkey's burnt!
Potatoes are ruined! Potatoes
are ruined! Potatoes are ruined!
감자도 망쳤구!
감자 다 망쳤다구!
우리가 간다,
거리를 걸으며...
Here we come
Walking down the
엄마가 음식을 태웠었나?
This doesn't smell like Mom's.
아니, 그런 적 없어
It doesn't, does it? You wanted lumps?
Here you go, buddy. You got one!
오빠가 원했던 덩어리 감자는
바로 여기 있어
소리치지마
태워먹은 건 너야
-Don't yell at me. You burned dinner!
-Hey, don't make her squeak again!
쟤 성질 좀 건들지마
아주 잘됐다!
God, this is great! The plane is gone.
I guess I'm stuck here with you guys.
비행기는 날아갔으니
여기 너희들과 있어야 돼
We all had better plans.
This was nobody's first choice!
우리 모두 계획이 있었어
계획대로 된 건 없지만
관둬!
Oh, really? So why was I busting
my ass to make this delicious dinner?
난 그 잘난 요리하느라
힘들어 죽을 뻔했어
- 누가 시켰냐?
- 다 너 때문이야
-You call that delicious?
-You be quiet!
관둬, 그만해!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
이게 진짜 추수감사절이야
Now this feels like Thanksgiving.
스키다...
Skiing.
슉
Shoop, shoop, shoop....
슉!
Shoop.
어머!
-Eww.
-What?
왜?
못생긴 남자가 오븐에서
칠면조를 꺼낸다
Ugly Naked Guy's taking his turkey
out of the oven.
-Who cares?
-He just sat in gravy.
저런 느끼 덩어리들!
세상에!
혼자가 아니야
Oh, my God! He's not alone.
못생긴 남자가 벗은 여자들과
추수감사절 저녁을 먹는다
Ugly Naked Guy is having Thanksgiving
dinner with Ugly Naked Gal.
나도 봐야지
I gotta see this!
아저씨 신나겠어요
All right, Ugly Naked Guy!
춤도 되게 못 추네
Ugly naked dancing!
함께 있는 게 좋은 거야
It's nice that he has someone.
이제 자를까?
Shall I carve?
-By all means.
-All right.
맘대로 해
치즈 한 장 짜리?
석 장 짜리?
Who wants light cheese,
and who wants dark cheese?
I don't even want to know
about the dark cheese.
치즈 석 장 짜리는
좀 느글거리겠어
-Does anybody wanna split this?
-I will.
- 이거 나눠 먹을 사람?
- 나!
-You guys have to make a wish.
-Make a wish?
소원을 빌어야지
소원?
Come on, you know, Thanksgiving.
추수감사절 전통 몰라?
You got the bigger half!
What did you wish for?
그쪽이 더 크다!
소원이 뭐야?
더 큰 거 먹는 거
The bigger half.
내가 축사를 할게
모두 잔 들어
All right, I'd like
to propose a toast.
A little toast here. Ding, ding!
우리 각자가 원하던
추수감사절이 아닌 건 알아
This isn't the Thanksgiving
you planned...
하지만 내겐 최고야
...but for me,
this has been really great.
알다시피, 이혼 소식도 없고
토할 일도 없으니까
I think because it didn't involve
divorce or projectile vomiting.
레이첼이 베일에 갔거나
If you'd gone to Vail
or if you had been with your family...
너희 남매가 가족에게 갔거나
네가...
...or if you didn't have syphilis
and stuff...
성병에 걸리지 않았다면
...we wouldn't be together.
이렇게 모일 수 없었을 거야
그래서 참으로 감사함을 느껴
너희들 계획이 망가진 것을
I guess what l' m trying
to say is that...
... I' m very thankful that all
of your Thanksgivings sucked.
연설 잘 하네
-That's so sweet!
-Thank you.
성탄절도 엉망이기를!
-Here's to a lousy Christmas!
-And a crappy New Year!
송년회도 시시하기를!
-Hear, hear!
성병 : 누가 걸렸는지
아무도 모릅니다
방광에 염증이?
가정 폭력 추방
치질 있으세요?
토니상 3회 수상